(Sheldon:)She's always complaining
about people at work.
(Penny:)Well, so does Leonard.
(Penny:)It's kind of annoying, but
it's not the end of the world.
(Sheldon:)Do you know that when I get out
of the shower,
(Sheldon:)she eyes me up and down
like I'm a piece of meat?
(Penny:)You know, so does Leonard.
(Penny:)Can't I just get ready
in the morning
(Penny:)without him giving me
his goofy thumbs-up?
"Hey."
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Sheldon:)Sometimes I would just like
to be appreciated for my mind.
Agreed!
Thank you!
(Bernadette:)That feels great.
(Howard:)Well,
(Howard:)pulling a quarter out
of your ear
(Howard:)isn't the only magic
these hands can do.
In fact, wh-what's this
between your toes?!
(Bernadette:)Can you please stop making money
come out of me for two minutes?
(Bernadette:)Was that the front door?
(Howard:)It sounded like it.
(Howard:)Oh, my God.
Someone's in the house.
Lock the door, lock the door!